Hello everyone, how are you all?  I, your
BFSI mentor Ekta Huja, have joined you again today with
a new job vacancy. So
how are you my BFSI aspirants? I hope
you all are doing very well and are rocking a lot.
Today's job opening in the BFSI industry is
in ICICI Lobbard. See, I keep bringing
different job vacancies on a regular basis.
Today's job vacancy is
specifically for the life insurance company ICI
Lobbard and the name of the
job profile that has come out in this insurance company is
Customer Care Officer Sir.
This is the job profile of Navi Mumbai.  So all the kids
join quickly because I am going to start today's job
vacancy.  But
before that, if you want the link of the job vacancy, then
you will get the link of the job vacancy in the description box.
Go and see this vacancy.
Then copy the job vacancy link
and apply for it quickly.  So let's
quickly start today's job
vacancy.  So the name of the job vacancy is Customer
Care Officer
and this job vacancy has
come out in ICICI Lombard in Navi Mumbai.  We all know that
ICICI LBD is a leading life insurance
company and most of the life insurance
products are sold by it.  So here we
talk about JD.  So first of all the
name of the designation, the name of the job role,
that is Customer Care Officer.  After that, if I
talk about the location, its location is Navi Mumbai.
This job vacancy is
for both freshers and experienced.  Zero to
five years experience is required in this.
So both freshers and those who have experience can
apply for this.  The job
is full time.  Graduation is required.  Any
stream graduation: Any stream
graduate will be eligible.  There is nothing specifically mentioned in this
that B.Com, BBA, B.Sc etc. are
required.  It only says
graduation.  It is a full time job and take a
look at the number of openings.  30 number of openings are
found in it.
Come on CTC son, CTC is not in the job opening in this.  The
job where
you have the vacancy link does not have CTC mentioned in it.
That's why I have removed CTC here
because it is currently not
disclosed.  Only when you go for the
interview, you will know
how much CTC that company is offering you.
Now let us talk about JD, let us
talk about what you have to do as a customer care officer.  So first of all
you have to solve the customer's complaint
in a timely and professional manner.
You have to solve all the complaints that customers are bringing to you.  You have to give
accurate information about the product and service to the customer.
If a customer
asks you about a product or service,
you have to accurately tell that customer about that product and
service.
After that comes Process Orders Returns
and Service Requests.  Whatever
service request the customer has, whether the customer is ordering something
or talking about a return,
you have to process all those service requests.
Next is our
maintaining customer records in the system.
You have to maintain customer records in the system,
which customer you
talked to, what related matter you discussed, what service was discussed,
and you will record the entire call lock in it.
Escalate unresolved issue to the
concerned department.  If there is any issue
which you are unable to solve or
needs escalation, then
you will escalate it to the department for which the issue is
and you will maintain a high customer
satisfaction level.
Here, if I look at this job profile, the
sales part will be very less.
Because here JD has
not written about sales.  Apart From This One
Apart From This One is
not written about sales anywhere.  So I think this is
pure customer care officer job where you can
apply easily.  And if this offer is
for freshers then go ahead and
apply.  All the children from Navi Mumbai or nearby areas,
please apply and go and give the interview.
So that was all the job openings for today.  I
hope you guys will go, apply and
tell us about your jobs in the comment section.
So let me tell you again,
you will get the apply link in the job description.
From there you
can easily apply for it.  So again
as I always do
I will get back to you in the next job vacancy.  Till then
take care.  Happy
applying and definitely apply.  Ok?
Bye-bye.